

Dmytro Lazarenko

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Email: Lazarenkodmitr@gmail.com LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp, Tel: +49 174 191 4692

Weimar, Germany Ready to work remotely / move

I am looking for a job as a junior frontend developer in an interesting company where I can improve my skills and become better every day. I have a technical education and one year of experience in frontend development. I am focused on creating responsive websites and web applications. I have experience with JavaScript, Typescript, React, HTML, CSS.

SKILLS

Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 - 2019) React
HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM,
Responsive web design, Photoshop,
Figma
Git/Github, VS Code
Basic OOP understanding

LANGUAGES

English: Strong Intermediate (B2) Polisch: Strong Intermediate (B2) Russich: Proficiency (C1) German: Intermediate (B1) Ukrainian: Native language (C2)

EDUCATION

09.2003 - 02.2009

National Technical University

Master's degree in computer engineering and automation

10.2022 - 10.2023

Frontend development course at Mate academy



EXPERIENCE

Januar 2023 - Present

Frontend Developer, Training projects: JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Responsive web design My Portfolio

08.2016 - 10.2022

Manager of the supply department of network fuel stations / Gemini espresso

Kyiv, Ukraine

Organized work with the supply, maintenance and regular deliveries coffee and coffee maschinen to 400 petrol stations in Ukraine. Supply of equipment and work with chain clients in

FMCG market. Record-keeping SRM.

Constant teamwork

09.2015 - 06.2016

Electrical Engineer / Grupa Reesco

Warsaw, Poland

Engineering projects of led lighting, electrical engineering, internet networking, alarm system and energy efficient technology

08.2010 - 09.2015

Service Technician

Kyiv, Ukraine

Repair of electrical devices,

Reporting, on-site work at the customer's location.

09.2009 - 08.2010

Electrical Engineer / Grupa MHP

Ukraine

Construction of the electrical part of the factory, connection of power units, laying of cables, connection of low-voltage lines,

commissioning, troubleshooting, and ongoing maintenance.